A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 36 FA307
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Visual Materials Separated from Grants, 1924-1981; 750 prints
  - New York State - Pneumonia Program - Agenda and Minutes, 1935-1937; 2 prints (Box 79, Folder 95)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 249, Folder 2379
  - State University of New York (Downstate Medical Center) - Recruitment of Faculty to the Department of Anatomy and Cell Biology, 1979-1981 (Box 79, Folder 96)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 250, Folder 2387
  - New York University (College of Medicine) - Department of Preventive Medicine - General Support, 1937-1947; 2 prints (Box 79, Folder 97)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 250, Folder 2391
  - New York University (College of Medicine) - Department of Psychiatry and Neurology - Cerebral Function Studies, 1947-1956; 44 prints (Box 79, Folder 98-99)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 251, Folder 2399-2400
  - New York University (College of Medicine) - Department of Psychiatry and Neurology - Cerebral Function Studies (Material Abstracts), 1952; 12 prints (Box 79, Folder 100)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 252, Folder 2402
  - New York University (College of Medicine) - Research in Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1936-1942; 12 prints (Box 79, Folder 101)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 254, Folder 2422
  - New York University (Department of Biology) - Means to Increase Resistance to Low Atmospheric Pressures, 1943-1946; 20 prints (Box 79, Folder 102)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 255, Folder 102
  - Northwestern University (Medical School) - Integrated Program for Medical Education, 1958-1968; 2 prints (Box 79, Folder 103-104)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 259, Folder 2479 and Box 260, Folder 2481.
  - Notre Dame Bay Memorial Hospital - General Support, 1924-1934; 26 prints (Box 79, Folder 105-106)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 260, Folder 2485-2486
  - Oklahoma State Medical Association - Postgraduate Instruction in Obstetrics, 1938-1944; 1 print (Box 79, Folder 107)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 262, Folder 2502
  - University of Pennsylvania (Gynecean Hospital) - Institute of Gynecologic Research - Familial Distribution of Cancer of the Breast Study, 1948-1958; 5 prints (Box 79, Folder 108)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 267, Folder 2549
  - University of Pennsylvania (Henry Phipps Institute) - Resistance and Susceptibility to Experimental Tuberculosis Study, 1941-1962; 9 prints (Box 79, Folder 109-110)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 268, Folder 2562 and 2564
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941; 21 prints (Box 79, Folder 111-114)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 269, Folder 2572-25773 and Box 270, Folder 2578 and 2581.
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946; 25 prints (Box 79, Folder 115-118)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 271, Folder 2582-2584, 2588
  - University of Pennsylvania - Research Laboratories in Connection with the New Gynecological-Obstetrical Hospital, 1938-1947; 1 print (Box 79, Folder 119)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 271, Folder 2592
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Department of Bacteriology - Streptococcus Study, 1940-1943; 3 prints (Box 79, Folder 120)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 275, Folder 2621
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Consortium of West Philadelphia Mental Health, 1969 May 5-9; 1 print (Box 79, Folder 121)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 275, Folder 2625
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney, 1931-1935; 20 prints (Box 79, Folder 122-125)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 277, Folder 2644-2648
  - Population Council, Inc. - Implementation of Family Planning in Large Delivery Hospitals, 1965-1969; 2 prints (Box 79, Folder 126-127)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 285, Folder 2718-2719
  - University of Puerto Rico (School of Medicine) - Library, 1961-1970; CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, (Box 79, Folder 128-130)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 289, Folder 2750-2751, 2753
  - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene, Inc. (Columbia University, College of Physicians and Surgeons, Department of Psychiatry) - Development of a Laboratory for Observing Human Behavior (ME), 1954-1970; 1 print (Box 79, Folder 131)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 290, Folder 2764
  - University of Rochester (School of Medicine and Dentistry) - New Program of Medical Education, 1964; 4 prints (Box 79, Folder 132)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 292, Folder 2794
  - University of Chicago, 5 prints (Box 80, Folder 133)
  - Baylor University, 20 prints (Box 80, Folder 134)
  - University of Colorado, 21 prints (Box 80, Folder 135-136)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (WNET Channel 13) - Support for Major Capital and Program Development, 1975-1978; 22 prints (Box 80, Folder 137)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18, Box 103, Folder 936
  - The Exploritorium - The Program in Science Education and General Support, 1976-1980; 3 prints (Box 80, Folder 138)
  - University of Florida, 21 prints (Box 80, Folder 139-144)
  - University of Arkansas Medical Center (Box 81, Folder 145-146)
- Visual Materials Separated from Division of Publications, 1950-1981; Approximately 32 prints and slides
  - Stryer, Lubert - "Biochemestry", 1971 February 26; 19 slides (Box 82, Folder 147)
    CWF, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13, Box 16, Folder 160.
  - Squire, Lucy F. - "Fundamentals of Roentgenology", 1966 March 24-1979 September 30 (Box 82, Folder 148)
    CWF, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13, Box 16, Folder 155
  - Haman, Conrac C. - "Harkness House", 1978-1981; 10 prints (Box 82, Folder 149)
    CWF, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13, Box 38, Folder 391
  - Books Received - Cockshott, W. Peter and Howard Middlemiss - "Clinical Radiology in the Tropics", 1977-1981; 3 prints (Box 82, Folder 150)
    CWF, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13, Box 25, Folder 229
  - Grob, Gerald N. - "Report on Insanity and Idiocy in Massachusetts" (Jarvis Report), 1966-1971 (Box 82, Folder 151)
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Galleys I), 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 152-154)
    CWF, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13, Box 47, Folder 491-493
  - Talbot, Nathan - "Functional Endocrinology" (Illustrations), 1951 May 3 (Box 83, Folder 155-159)
    CWF, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13, Box 47, Folder 494-495